[Music]
the sagas gone Jacob and Esau here are
two brothers they were at war already
[Music]
Jacob came into this world with his hand
on Esau steel tried to pull him back
inside he always wanted to be the person
[Applause]
if I was a hunter check out my stove
so I was a man of passion
he's our size and Sam
Jacob s it's always hard and ever she
gonna
bludgeon
mother just the bureaucrat destroy most
Atlanta they were
ready
already
[Music]
scholar and the warrior shall be lead
shall be torn chosen and the proletarian
veteran me
brother shot my brother discord reign
among the tribes
to the hardship coming in
body shop
exactly
until they are stolen piece
two people with us were made yet I'll
let you fire in just
reconcile make sure
already
[Music]
you